<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Descy</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/mjdescy&quot;&gt;@mjdescy on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:18:37 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:18:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>It looks like Essential is going away</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-05-24/andy-rubin-s-phone-maker-essential-is-said-to-consider-sale&quot;&gt;Android Creator Puts Essential Up for Sale, Cancels Next Phone - Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Current discussions are focused on a sale of the entire company, including its patent portfolio, hardware products like the original smartphone, an upcoming smart home device and a camera attachment for the phone, said the people, who asked not to be identified because the talks are private.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got an Essential Phone in its release date, and was optimistic that the company would succeed. It looks like it hasn’t. Their first phone &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; have a bad camera experience (hardware and software-wise), which probably prevented any chance of success from the start. The Pixel and the Galaxy phones put it to shame. Plus, it must be next to impossible to make money selling Android phones. It’s not a business I would want to be in.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:18:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/24/001805.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/25/001805.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;📺 I’m enjoying the “remix” version of “Arrested Development” season 4 a lot better than the original version. I’m sure time passing and my expectations being lowered helped, but I prefer to see all (most) of the characters in the same episodes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 12:16:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/24/im-enjoying-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/24/im-enjoying-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was so busy today that I forgot to blog! Hours of data analysis and database development will do that to me. It’s a beautiful sunny evening, and I’m heading off to a barbecue with my family now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 17:02:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/23/i-was-so.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/23/i-was-so.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m pretty proud of my Ulysses library setup—at least the top level folder structure. My subfolders need a bit more organization, though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/1115f805e0.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 20:27:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/im-pretty-proud.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/23/im-pretty-proud.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 First listen: Mean Girls (Original Broadway Cast)</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/mean-girls-original-broadway-cast-recording/1372106911&quot;&gt;Mean Girls (Original Broadway Cast)&lt;/a&gt; is up for the Tony for best musical this year, and I think it has a legitimate shot. While this &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a weak year for the American musical, the music of “Mean Girls” is fun and catchy, and the lyrics are funny and full of wordplay. The singing and production of the cast album are top notch, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like it. The high school setting and girl-centric plot, though not the music, remind me a lot of “Bring It On”, which is another musical that has a fantastic cast album and works a lot better than you would think. I don’t know if this show will be a hit on Broadway, but I predict a long life on high school drama club stages in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 16:08:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/first-listen-mean.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/first-listen-mean.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎧 Headphones review: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/review/RFS8V3M6O5RUK/&quot;&gt;Sony MDR-1AM2/B&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 11:14:17 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/headphones-review-sony.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/headphones-review-sony.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I used my iPad Pro and Pencil to teach my (kindergarten-age) daughter (👩‍🔬) some &lt;a href=&quot;http://bedtimemath.org&quot;&gt;bedtime math&lt;/a&gt; for the first time tonight. She loved writing the numbers in different colors in Apple Notes. I loved writing on something I could easily erase. It was really fun.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 21:54:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/21/i-used-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/i-used-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just submitted SwiftoDo 2.12.0 to the App Store. Hopefully it’s good enough! 😅 Expect a release toward the end of the week, if all goes well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 21:26:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/21/i-just-submitted.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/22/i-just-submitted.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So much to do today, I don’t even know where to begin…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 10:37:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/21/so-much-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/21/so-much-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I took a new pair of headphones for a spin this evening. I think I may have a problem. 🎧😂&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 23:50:32 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/20/i-took-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/21/i-took-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mjdescy.me/2018/05/20/recess-and-good-bones-or-selling-the-world-to-my-children/&quot;&gt;“Recess” and “Good Bones”, or selling the world to my children&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 09:12:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/20/blog-post-recess.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/20/blog-post-recess.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; testing and fixing things in my dev build of SwiftoDo 2.12.0. It feels weird to have gone so long without issuing a release. I hope to get everything done next week. I have a very full weekend of family activities ahead of me, though, so I can’t do much till Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 19:43:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/im-still-testing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/im-still-testing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 Carry On</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On this bad and sad news day, remember:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you’re lost and alone&lt;br /&gt;
Or you’re sinking like a stone&lt;br /&gt;
Carry on&lt;br /&gt;
May your past be the sound&lt;br /&gt;
Of your feed upon the ground and&lt;br /&gt;
Carry on&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;‘Cause we are, we are shining stars&lt;br /&gt;
We are invincible&lt;br /&gt;
We are who we are&lt;br /&gt;
On our darkest day&lt;br /&gt;
When we’re miles away&lt;br /&gt;
So we’ll come, we will find our way home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fun.’s “Carry On” works well, and feels quite different, in &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/carry-on-feat-shannon-purser-rise-cast-version/1382637611?i=1382638029&quot;&gt;this cover version by the cast of “Rise”&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 16:31:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/carry-on-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/carry-on-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 Frozen: The Broadway Musical</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Listening to the cast recording of “&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/frozen-broadway-musical-original-broadway-cast-recording/1378411252&quot;&gt;Frozen: The Broadway Musical&lt;/a&gt;” for the first time is a bit surreal for me.  Compared to the movie, there are new songs, lyrics changes in existing songs, and, of course, different singers. I don’t think any of the changes are for the better. It’s hard to say for sure, though, because, as a parent of a little girl, I’ve heard the movie and the movie soundtrack about 1,000 times already, and it’s burned into my brain.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 15:21:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/frozen-the-broadway.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/frozen-the-broadway.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While I think I &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; a Nintendo Switch, I’m trying to make due for now with what I already have—an iPad Pro and a SteelSeries Nimbus controller. I’m not sure I even want to commit the &lt;em&gt;time&lt;/em&gt; to gaming, but I am curious about the latest Mario and Zelda games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/9800db785e.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 10:16:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/while-i-think.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/while-i-think.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mjdescy.me/2018/05/17/the-calm-before-the-wwdc-storm/&quot;&gt;The calm before the WWDC storm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 23:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/17/blog-post-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/blog-post-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google’s attractive but less information dense redesign of Google News may be the thing that finally breaks my addiction to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/c4fea0b7e1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 22:00:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/17/googles-attractive-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/18/googles-attractive-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Google's music and video streaming strategy is a mess</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.engadget.com/2018/05/17/google-play-youtube-music-premium-strategy/&quot;&gt;Engadget has it right&lt;/a&gt;. I have no idea what Google audio/video service I should ever consider subscribing to, and because music is tied in there, they don’t offer what I want (ad-free YouTube) at price that is reasonable to me. Maybe it doesn’t matter, because Google will just fold it and create an alternative service, with a different name, price, and product mix, in a couple years anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As much as I rely on Google Search, and as much as I use, indifferently, Gmail, I just don’t understand Google as a company. Their central strategy appears to be “no strategy”. They try stuff out, kill it if it fails, and iterate on what succeeds. This process is fun to watch when the company is a young startup, but is a bit much to bear when they are one of the four pillars of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If my kids didn’t love YouTube, but hate the ads, I wouldn’t think about subscribing to YouTube Premium (or is it YouTube Red? or is it YouTube Music?) at all. If Google cared about customers like me—very light YouTube viewers who would pay a small amount of money to not be interrupted by ads—I would send them some money each month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 12:28:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/17/googles-music-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/17/googles-music-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My brain’s boot-up time is taking longer than usual today. ☕️☕️☕️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 09:14:32 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/17/my-brains-bootup.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/17/my-brains-bootup.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;cast&lt;/em&gt; of &lt;em&gt;Solo&lt;/em&gt; certainly is  appealing, even if &lt;a href=&quot;https://slate.com/culture/2018/05/solo-the-new-star-wars-movie-reviewed.html&quot;&gt;the movie itself may be largely inconsequential&lt;/a&gt;. To think, I used to care more about the &lt;em&gt;director&lt;/em&gt; than the cast. 🎬&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:09:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/the-cast-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/16/the-cast-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;SwiftoDo 2.12.0 was looking pretty dire last night, but is now looking like it may be ready for release, thanks to some improvements I made today. I will do more testing this week to make sure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 19:08:49 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/swiftodo-was-looking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/swiftodo-was-looking.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Work has been heating up for me lately, which is good all around, but a change nonetheless. It’s good to have lots of work to look forward to each day. It’s bad to feel like there’s so much you can’t finish each day, too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 17:05:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/work-has-been.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/work-has-been.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Am I late to the game with using semaphores, or are all the cool (cool?) kids using them these days?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 10:16:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/am-i-late.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/am-i-late.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m loving the second season of “Westworld” so far. I can’t wait to see how it all comes together in the end.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:59:17 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/im-loving-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/im-loving-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been testing what I thought would be SwiftoDo’s next release build all day. All day, Dropbox has been throwing error messages, making me think my code is messed up. Now, the same code is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; throwing those error messages. It must be internet weather or something.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 21:59:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/14/015943.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/15/015943.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a great Mother’s Day. Probably the best I can remember. We just spent it at home, and at my in-laws’ home, with family.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 22:26:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/13/today-was-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/14/today-was-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>From Spotify to Indie and Beyond: A Top Dev Interview With John Sundell</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed this interview with Swift expert, blogger, and podcaster John Sundell (&lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/johnsundell&quot;&gt;@johnsundell&lt;/a&gt;): 
&lt;a href=&quot;https:/z/www.raywenderlich.com/192589/from-spotify-to-indie-and-beyond-a-top-dev-interview-with-john-sundell&quot;&gt;From Spotify to Indie and Beyond: A Top Dev Interview With John Sundell&lt;/a&gt;. I have learned a lot from John’s weekly blog, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.swiftbysundell.com&quot;&gt;Swift by Sundell&lt;/a&gt;, in the past year or so, and always enjoy his contributions to the Swift programming community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 13:16:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/11/from-spotify-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/11/from-spotify-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 Frightened Rabbit singer commits suicide 😥</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;(My original title was just an expletive.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-44079462&quot;&gt;Body confirmed as missing Frightened Rabbit singer - BBC News&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Depression is a horrendous illness that does not give you any alert or indication as to when it will take hold of you”, it added.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“Scott battled bravely with his own issues for many years and we are immensely proud of him for being so open with his struggles.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“His willingness to discuss these matters in the public domain undoubtedly raised awareness of mental health issues and gave others confidence and belief to discuss their own issues.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m so upset. I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; Frightened Rabbit. It was no secret that Scott Hutchison suffered from depression, anxiety, and who knows what else—it’s &lt;em&gt;all over&lt;/em&gt; his arch, wry lyrics. Go listen to “&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/keep-yourself-warm/917524230?i=917524306&quot;&gt;Keep Yourself Warm&lt;/a&gt;” to get an idea of what a great singer/songwriter he was.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 09:49:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/11/frightened-rabbit-singer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/11/frightened-rabbit-singer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Pure Gold from Pinboard's FAQ</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I came across this tonight, as I was perusing &lt;a href=&quot;https://pinboard.in/faq/#cjk_search&quot;&gt;Pinboard’s FAQ&lt;/a&gt;, trying to learn something different about the service that I have been ignoring for the past year or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Is it true the site admin can see private bookmarks?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Yes. I routinely look at raw bookmark data, which includes private bookmarks. Most of the time this means I look at URLs without any identifying context.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;I try to avoid looking at private data on people’s individual pages. However, this is sometimes necessary in order to diagnose and fix bugs in Pinboard, such as search errors, or strange formatting in archived pages.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;I use the metaphor of a hotel manager. I have a key that opens every room, but I try not to use it without a good reason. &lt;strong&gt;And I can assure everyone that five years of running this site has eliminated any trace of curiosity I might have had about what people bookmark.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Emphasis is my own. 🤣)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 21:25:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/10/pure-gold-from.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/11/pure-gold-from.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to install some iOS games with MFi controller support on my iPad Pro. But…will I actually find time to play them? 🤷‍♂️&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/41dc26e584.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 15:48:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/10/i-decided-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/10/i-decided-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I discovered this great &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/guides/crosswords/how-to-solve-a-crossword-puzzle&quot;&gt;primer on the New York Times crossword puzzle&lt;/a&gt; (and crosswords in general) today. I wish I had known earlier that the &lt;em&gt;Saturday&lt;/em&gt; puzzle, not the Sunday one, is the most difficult of the week.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 08:47:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/10/i-discovered-this.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/10/i-discovered-this.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am finding new people to follow every day or so on Micro.blog—mainly through the Discover feature, occasionally from Mentions, and weekly through the Micro Monday podcast. It is a slow but rewarding process.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 20:02:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/09/i-am-finding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/10/i-am-finding.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The Best Trackballs according to Wirecutter</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Wirecutter updated its &lt;a href=&quot;https://thewirecutter.com/reviews/best-trackballs/?utm_source=rss&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=RSS%20Feed&quot;&gt;trackballs review&lt;/a&gt; today. Their recommendations are basically unchanged, which is no surprise, because the entire trackball market has been stagnant for years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the lack of evolution in trackballs, I am a huge fan of them. I credit swapping my mouse for a trackball with reducing, to almost nothing, repetitive stress injuries from computing. I find trackballs to be more comfortable to use and more precise than both mice and trackpads. I actually have one for each my my machines (Mac and PC), and bring the smaller one with me when I travel for work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t quibble with WireCutter’s top pick, but I disagree with their assessment of my main trackball, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kensington.com/en/ae/4493/k72327eu/slimblade-trackball&quot;&gt;Kensington SlimBlade&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Instead of using a hardware scroll ring as on the Kensington Expert Mouse and Orbit with Scroll Ring, with the Kensington SlimBlade Trackball you have to rotate the ball to scroll, which is tough to do without bouncing the cursor around the screen. The SlimBlade’s buttons feel hollow compared with the Expert Mouse’s, and its shiny plastic and metal surfaces attract fingerprints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, its buttons could be a little clickier, but rotating the ball to scroll without moving the cursor is actually pretty easy. Unlike the Expert Mouse, the SlimBlade doesn’t have an unnecessarily steep angle to it, so you can use it comfortably without a wrist rest. And, honestly, saying its “surfaces attract fingerprints” is just plain stupid. My iPad Pro screen, which is the finest screen in my entire house, “attracts fingerprints” too. I think product reviewers need to strike that quibble off their list.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 13:50:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/09/the-best-trackballs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/09/the-best-trackballs.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Improving Dropbox-related error messages in SwiftoDo</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve done a lot of work rewriting the Dropbox code in &lt;a href=&quot;https://swiftodoapp.com&quot;&gt;SwiftoDo&lt;/a&gt;. At this point, any error messages it generates are a now a little less well written—they are more generic—but they will appear more quickly, with greater consistency, and will reappear (as you would expect) each time Dropbox is accessed until the problem is fixed. Plus, the new error messages will provide a &lt;em&gt;little&lt;/em&gt; more information about what went wrong than they did before. I hope it’s the right tradeoff.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:02:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/09/improving-dropboxrelated-error.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/09/improving-dropboxrelated-error.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 Okkervil River's back catalog</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Listening to Okkervil River’s new album, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/in-the-rainbow-rain/1342462882&quot;&gt;In the Rainbow Rain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, today gave me an excuse to dive, once again, into their back catalog. I am a huge fan of the band’s 2005-2008 work, a trifecta of literate rock albums: &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/black-sheep-boy-10th-anniversary-edition/1036936862&quot;&gt;Black Sheep Boy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/the-stand-ins/543561172&quot;&gt;The Stand Ins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/the-stage-names-bonus-track-version/453256340&quot;&gt;The Stage Names&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Each of these albums is a staggering artistic achievement; each song on them is an evocative short story with enough weight, depth, and maturity to reward repeated listenings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t spent nearly as many hours listening to their work since then, which which includes &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/the-silver-gymnasium/977288852&quot;&gt;The Silver Gymnasium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/away/1113050258&quot;&gt;Away&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. This, more recent, period is characterized by a darker, more somber tone. It’s easy to imagine the band’s frontman, and only consistent member now, Will Sheff, slowing down, looking back on life, and looking far forward to his eventual death. That’s way heavier stuff than what I normally listen to, but not &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; heavy to be enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:01:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/okkervil-rivers-back.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/okkervil-rivers-back.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Trying to get back into Pinboard, or, maybe I am over-complicating things</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am trying to get back into &lt;a href=&quot;https://pinboard.in&quot;&gt;Pinboard&lt;/a&gt;, the reliable and, a few years ago, faddish, “antisocial” bookmarking service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had been using it as an archive of my old browser bookmarks, and as a “read it later” service to push articles to from Twitter and my RSS reader. I used to use it pretty consistently, with the help of an iOS app and a Chrome plugin for my Mac. When I went on an RSS and Twitter diet late last year, though, I kicked my Pinboard app off my phone as well. More recently, I wiped my Mac clean and reinstalled a bare minimum of apps and services, which did not include Chrome or the whatever Pinboard plugin I had been using with Safari. Since then, Safari and Google have been my bookmarking service, in that I don’t actually save any bookmarks, but rely on typing URLs or searches directly into the browser address bar most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, in part because iOS supports it in the long-press menu on every URL, I have been saving links to Apple’s built-in Safari Reading List. Saving bookmarks is as low-friction as can be, but reading them is, paradoxically, very high friction for me. I never think to dig into the second panel within Safari’s bookmarks to look for something to read. Consequently, my Safari Reading List has become a graveyard for links that I (think I) want to read but probably never will. Maybe that’s what is is actually for, and maybe that’s what I actually need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For fun, though, I’m going to try to use Pinboard more instead.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 10:44:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/trying-to-get.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/trying-to-get.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Micro Monday: Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/matigo&quot;&gt;@matigo&lt;/a&gt;. He’s a lot like me, but lives halfway across the world (in Japan as opposed to New Jersey). He posts and replies to posts frequently, and is a great member of the Micro.blog community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:04:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/micro-monday-follow.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/micro-monday-follow.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Robocalls Flooding Your Cellphone? Here’s How to Stop Them</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nyti.ms/2q5d7oj&quot;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt; inspired me to install &lt;a href=&quot;https://gethiya.app.link/phone-guard&quot;&gt;Hiya&lt;/a&gt; on my iPhone to block spam calls. I will find out eventually how well it works. I get 5-10 robocalls per week, mostly from the same exchange as my mobile number or my Google Voice number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems to rely on a central service for all blocking rules, including an optional whitelist for your contacts and an optional rule based on your phone number for “neighbor” spam. It can identify and block a gigantic list of known spammers and robocallers, which is beyond what I need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having looked at it, and its competition, it seems like there isn’t a good on-device-only call blocker for the super-privacy conscious who, like me, only want to whitelist contacts and blacklist all other numbers in a couple of area codes and exchanges. I really want to write one. It would have to be free, I think, based on the free competition out there—but it may fit a particular niche that is out there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:09:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/07/robocalls-flooding-your.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/08/robocalls-flooding-your.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Google Plus still exists. Why?</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven’t thought about this in a long time, but I am actually surprised that &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com&quot;&gt;Google Plus&lt;/a&gt; still exists. Considering how many products Google launches and kills each year for practically no reason, it’s astounding that one of its monumental flops has been allowed to limp along for so many years. I think it must still be around because either it still generates signals for Google (how many though, compared to other things?), or because it was tied in, at a technical level, to more valuable and integral services like Gmail. All I know is that its continued presence in the Google portfolio serves as yet another reminder to me about how unfocused Google is as an organization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 21:10:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/06/google-plus-still.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/07/google-plus-still.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m making 12-bean soup today, in an effort to get back to eating home-cooked, wholesome foods. Every few months, as work and family commitments change, my family gets off track. Hopefully we can right the ship now that is is spring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/e977b23e44.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 11:12:49 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/06/im-making-bean.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/06/im-making-bean.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>My 300th post on Micro.blog</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;According to my Account page, this is my 300th post on Micro.blog. I thought I would share some stats:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Micro.blog posts: 300&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Days on the platform: 136 (joined 2017-12-19)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Average posts per day: 2.2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How many people I follow: 131&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How many people follow me: I have no idea, and that is fine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much engagement I get from other users: a pleasingly good amount&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much I happily paid Manton for Micro.blog hosting thus far: $30 USD ($5/month, not including the free trial period)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How little I could have paid, if I wanted: $0 for a WordPress.com blog or $1/month for an inexpensive WordPress host, plus the free Micro.blog account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Micro.blog has gotten me into blogging again after a long time away from it. I enjoy owning my own content, the focus on &lt;em&gt;writing&lt;/em&gt; rather than liking or retweeting, and, most of all, the lack of &lt;em&gt;friction&lt;/em&gt; in the platform.  Posting short or long form content is as simple as can be, and I don’t have a WordPress install and/or server to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am having fun on the platform and look forward to continuing to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 21:17:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/my-th-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/05/my-th-post.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Google News is getting more video</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/4/17320190/google-news-update-video-youtube-amp&quot;&gt;Google News is getting a revamp with more video and faster load times - The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Google is giving Google News a redesign that will bring in elements from its Newsstand app and YouTube, according to sources who spoke with AdAge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More video? Gee, no thanks! Maybe I should give Apple News a try again…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 20:26:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/google-news-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/05/google-news-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 Groundhog Day the Musical</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/groundhog-day-musical-original-broadway-cast-recording/1215389487&quot;&gt;Groundhog Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is my second favorite Broadway musical of last year (closely behind “Dear Evan Hansen”, which has more plot-related problems but really terrific music), and the only one I saw. I revisit the cast album from time to time, because it is terrific, and multiple listens reveal hidden depth in the earthy lyrics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.broadwayworld.com/article/BWW-CD-Review-GROUNDHOG-DAY-THE-MUSICAL-Original-Broadway-Cast-Recording-is-Charmingly-Animated-20170516&quot;&gt;Broadway World’s review of the cast album&lt;/a&gt; is remarkably spot on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On first listen, Minchin’s melodies are captivating. They are undeniably more poppy than his dark, moody, and undulating score for MATILDA; however, it’s obvious that he has written each of these compositions with the same consideration and care that he did with MATILDA. Despite the more simplistic sounding and pop aural soundscape, the melodies are intricately layered showing an artistry and skill that is not apparent in one listening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Tim Minchin keeps writing musicals. His music and lyrics for his prior show, &lt;em&gt;Matilda&lt;/em&gt;, are a masterpiece. (Listen to the London cast recording over the Broadway one if you can; it is a &lt;em&gt;far&lt;/em&gt; better performance, though it is missing some of Matilda’s monologues.) “Groundhog Day” doesn’t quite rank as a masterpiece in my book, but it is really, really good.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 19:35:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/groundhog-day-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/groundhog-day-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Listening to Podcasts without Voice Boost</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; accustomed to listening to Podcasts with &lt;a href=&quot;https://overcast.fm&quot;&gt;Overcast&lt;/a&gt;’s “Voice Boost” feature that, when I turn it off (as I’m doing today, because my Bluetooth headphones are too loud) my podcasts sound flat and lifeless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder, though, why more podcast producers don’t run their episodes through dynamic compression and EQ filters (“Voice Boost”) prior to publishing. For that matter, why don’t they “shorten silences” on their end, too? That way, everyone could benefit from better audio quality and a shorter runtime. I suspect that some of big, radio-show-based podcasts do, but it’s obvious that most other podcasts don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 09:14:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/listening-to-podcasts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/listening-to-podcasts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The 2017 Panic Report</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://panic.com/blog/the-2017-panic-report/&quot;&gt;Panic Report&lt;/a&gt; is always worth a read. I use a lot of their apps, and have long considered them an app studio so talented that I will buy whatever they make, so long as I can sometimes use it. They are refreshingly open and honest about their business, too. Their annual reports are especially eye opening if you are a developer and are curious about the business aspects of the App Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought this part, toward the end, was kind of funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;⑨ I’m using Transmit 5 as my primary interface to Dropbox. Am I a bad person? —Kyle&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Absolutely not. This is so potentially powerful, we even made a video about it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t install Dropbox on my Mac anymore. Instead, I now use iCloud Drive for cross-device sync. I use Transmit 5 to get to Dropbox, the few times I need it. It seems weird to do so at first, but it is much lighter on resources, if you don’t need file sync.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 23:40:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/03/the-panic-report.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/the-panic-report.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Note to past self:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remind me again why you decided to rewrite, yet again, the Dropbox-related code in your app? You know, the code that you may just get rid of completely a few months from now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,
🤯&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 20:59:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/03/note-to-past.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/note-to-past.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I didn’t know about this action to post &lt;em&gt;directly&lt;/em&gt; from Drafts 5 to micro.blog, with or without a title, until today. It’s a game-changer for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://actions.getdrafts.com/a/1Hg&quot;&gt;Post to Micro.blog (with Title) - Drafts Action Directory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:50:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/i-didnt-know.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/i-didnt-know.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Two of the best platformers I've played on iOS are getting their due today from Apple</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Apple’s US App Store is highlighting two great games that are among the best on the platform:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/story/id1356375657&quot;&gt;Game of the Day: Goblin Sword&lt;/a&gt;. Goblin Sword plays like a AAA title from the 16-bit days, and has great play control, difficulty, and variety. It’s fantastic.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/story/id1369365671&quot;&gt;Games Are Art: The Beauty of Oddmar&lt;/a&gt;. I learned about Oddmar from someone else on micro.blog, and have only played through a handful of levels. The play controls are unique and well suited for the iPhone, and the graphics and sound are amazing. It’s a fun and funny game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 14:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/two-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/two-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Remote login Inception</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At work, our clients are far more interested in information security than they used to be. That’s great, and I applaud them for it. Of course, as a user of their systems, there is a trade-off in terms of convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately, logging into remote systems seems like entering a-dream-within-a-dream-within-a-dream—a la &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1375666/&quot;&gt;Inception&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Instead of merely using Remote Desktop to log into systems with a single username/password, we now follow in-depth login procedures using virtualization software, RSA tokens that generate unique, one-time passwords, Remote Desktop logins, and systems logins.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 11:26:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/remote-login-inception.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/remote-login-inception.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Who cares about Apple earnings reports?</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do Windows fans care about Microsoft’s earnings? Do Android fans care about Google’s? I wonder if the main reason Apple fans (non-investors) &lt;a href=&quot;https://sixcolors.com/post/2018/05/apple-quarterly-results-charts-live-tweets/&quot;&gt;cheer on Apple’s good earnings reports&lt;/a&gt; is that Apple almost went out of business in the 1990s. Unless the company is going out of business, or if you have tied a lot of your money up with them somehow, who cares about its quarterly earnings report?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 22:59:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/who-cares-about.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/who-cares-about.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
