<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Descy</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/mjdescy&quot;&gt;@mjdescy on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 21:17:29 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 21:17:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>My 300th post on Micro.blog</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;According to my Account page, this is my 300th post on Micro.blog. I thought I would share some stats:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Micro.blog posts: 300&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Days on the platform: 136 (joined 2017-12-19)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Average posts per day: 2.2&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How many people I follow: 131&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How many people follow me: I have no idea, and that is fine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much engagement I get from other users: a pleasingly good amount&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much I happily paid Manton for Micro.blog hosting thus far: $30 USD ($5/month, not including the free trial period)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How little I could have paid, if I wanted: $0 for a WordPress.com blog or $1/month for an inexpensive WordPress host, plus the free Micro.blog account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Micro.blog has gotten me into blogging again after a long time away from it. I enjoy owning my own content, the focus on &lt;em&gt;writing&lt;/em&gt; rather than liking or retweeting, and, most of all, the lack of &lt;em&gt;friction&lt;/em&gt; in the platform.  Posting short or long form content is as simple as can be, and I don’t have a WordPress install and/or server to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am having fun on the platform and look forward to continuing to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 21:17:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/my-th-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/05/my-th-post.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Google News is getting more video</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/4/17320190/google-news-update-video-youtube-amp&quot;&gt;Google News is getting a revamp with more video and faster load times - The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Google is giving Google News a redesign that will bring in elements from its Newsstand app and YouTube, according to sources who spoke with AdAge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More video? Gee, no thanks! Maybe I should give Apple News a try again…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 20:26:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/google-news-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/05/google-news-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 Groundhog Day the Musical</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/groundhog-day-musical-original-broadway-cast-recording/1215389487&quot;&gt;Groundhog Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is my second favorite Broadway musical of last year (closely behind “Dear Evan Hansen”, which has more plot-related problems but really terrific music), and the only one I saw. I revisit the cast album from time to time, because it is terrific, and multiple listens reveal hidden depth in the earthy lyrics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.broadwayworld.com/article/BWW-CD-Review-GROUNDHOG-DAY-THE-MUSICAL-Original-Broadway-Cast-Recording-is-Charmingly-Animated-20170516&quot;&gt;Broadway World’s review of the cast album&lt;/a&gt; is remarkably spot on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;On first listen, Minchin’s melodies are captivating. They are undeniably more poppy than his dark, moody, and undulating score for MATILDA; however, it’s obvious that he has written each of these compositions with the same consideration and care that he did with MATILDA. Despite the more simplistic sounding and pop aural soundscape, the melodies are intricately layered showing an artistry and skill that is not apparent in one listening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope Tim Minchin keeps writing musicals. His music and lyrics for his prior show, &lt;em&gt;Matilda&lt;/em&gt;, are a masterpiece. (Listen to the London cast recording over the Broadway one if you can; it is a &lt;em&gt;far&lt;/em&gt; better performance, though it is missing some of Matilda’s monologues.) “Groundhog Day” doesn’t quite rank as a masterpiece in my book, but it is really, really good.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 19:35:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/groundhog-day-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/groundhog-day-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Listening to Podcasts without Voice Boost</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; accustomed to listening to Podcasts with &lt;a href=&quot;https://overcast.fm&quot;&gt;Overcast&lt;/a&gt;’s “Voice Boost” feature that, when I turn it off (as I’m doing today, because my Bluetooth headphones are too loud) my podcasts sound flat and lifeless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder, though, why more podcast producers don’t run their episodes through dynamic compression and EQ filters (“Voice Boost”) prior to publishing. For that matter, why don’t they “shorten silences” on their end, too? That way, everyone could benefit from better audio quality and a shorter runtime. I suspect that some of big, radio-show-based podcasts do, but it’s obvious that most other podcasts don’t.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 09:14:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/listening-to-podcasts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/listening-to-podcasts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The 2017 Panic Report</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://panic.com/blog/the-2017-panic-report/&quot;&gt;Panic Report&lt;/a&gt; is always worth a read. I use a lot of their apps, and have long considered them an app studio so talented that I will buy whatever they make, so long as I can sometimes use it. They are refreshingly open and honest about their business, too. Their annual reports are especially eye opening if you are a developer and are curious about the business aspects of the App Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought this part, toward the end, was kind of funny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;⑨ I’m using Transmit 5 as my primary interface to Dropbox. Am I a bad person? —Kyle&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Absolutely not. This is so potentially powerful, we even made a video about it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t install Dropbox on my Mac anymore. Instead, I now use iCloud Drive for cross-device sync. I use Transmit 5 to get to Dropbox, the few times I need it. It seems weird to do so at first, but it is much lighter on resources, if you don’t need file sync.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 23:40:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/03/the-panic-report.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/the-panic-report.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Note to past self:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remind me again why you decided to rewrite, yet again, the Dropbox-related code in your app? You know, the code that you may just get rid of completely a few months from now?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,
🤯&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 20:59:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/03/note-to-past.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/04/note-to-past.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I didn’t know about this action to post &lt;em&gt;directly&lt;/em&gt; from Drafts 5 to micro.blog, with or without a title, until today. It’s a game-changer for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://actions.getdrafts.com/a/1Hg&quot;&gt;Post to Micro.blog (with Title) - Drafts Action Directory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:50:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/i-didnt-know.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/i-didnt-know.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Two of the best platformers I've played on iOS are getting their due today from Apple</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Apple’s US App Store is highlighting two great games that are among the best on the platform:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/story/id1356375657&quot;&gt;Game of the Day: Goblin Sword&lt;/a&gt;. Goblin Sword plays like a AAA title from the 16-bit days, and has great play control, difficulty, and variety. It’s fantastic.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/story/id1369365671&quot;&gt;Games Are Art: The Beauty of Oddmar&lt;/a&gt;. I learned about Oddmar from someone else on micro.blog, and have only played through a handful of levels. The play controls are unique and well suited for the iPhone, and the graphics and sound are amazing. It’s a fun and funny game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 14:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/two-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/two-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Remote login Inception</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At work, our clients are far more interested in information security than they used to be. That’s great, and I applaud them for it. Of course, as a user of their systems, there is a trade-off in terms of convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lately, logging into remote systems seems like entering a-dream-within-a-dream-within-a-dream—a la &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1375666/&quot;&gt;Inception&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Instead of merely using Remote Desktop to log into systems with a single username/password, we now follow in-depth login procedures using virtualization software, RSA tokens that generate unique, one-time passwords, Remote Desktop logins, and systems logins.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 11:26:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/remote-login-inception.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/remote-login-inception.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Who cares about Apple earnings reports?</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do Windows fans care about Microsoft’s earnings? Do Android fans care about Google’s? I wonder if the main reason Apple fans (non-investors) &lt;a href=&quot;https://sixcolors.com/post/2018/05/apple-quarterly-results-charts-live-tweets/&quot;&gt;cheer on Apple’s good earnings reports&lt;/a&gt; is that Apple almost went out of business in the 1990s. Unless the company is going out of business, or if you have tied a lot of your money up with them somehow, who cares about its quarterly earnings report?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 22:59:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/who-cares-about.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/02/who-cares-about.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>📚 Ready Player One, by Ernest Cline</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, I completed reading &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ready_Player_One&quot;&gt;Ready Player One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by Ernest Cline. It was the first novel that I had read in a while, as I have been reading mostly nonfiction in recent years. I discovered the book from an &lt;a href=&quot;https://twit.tv/shows/triangulation/episodes/322&quot;&gt;episode of the “Triangulation” podcast in which Leo Laporte interviewed author Andy Weir&lt;/a&gt;, who enthusiastically recommended the book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, I enjoyed the book. The prose is efficient and the pacing is swift. I thought it started out strong, and I liked the world building and the build-up of suspense in the early chapters. After a while, though, I tired of all the 1980s video game and movie references, and wanted the book to end. While I was about three quarters through the book, I referred to it as “the reading equivalent to watching somebody else play video games”. For me, the stakes felt too low, and the characterizations were too thin, to make a lasting impression. Still, I had fun reading it, at least most of the way through.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 16:13:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/201333.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/201333.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The best part of working from home is the ability to take a nice walk after lunch. Spring weather was finally here at lunchtime, and I thoroughly enjoyed it. Summer temperatures will follow by dinner time and last for the foreseeable future. So, that was spring!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/0efce021cd.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 14:27:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/the-best-part.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/the-best-part.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>I quit my iPhone for a basic Nokia and it was hard but worth it</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://qz.com/1264704/at-first-life-without-a-smartphone-was-terrifying-then-it-was-beautiful/&quot;&gt;This article on Quartz about limiting smartphone use&lt;/a&gt; is both sublime and ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I want to be present. Is that so much to ask for? Is that so odd to crave in this day and age?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Maybe you’re reading this thinking I’m taking it too far and being ridiculous. That it’s just a smartphone, people check them all the time and that’s just the way it is and I should get over it and get used to it. But being on it most of my free time feels wrong on every level. I don’t want to get used to it anymore. It shouldn’t be this hard to reduce the amount of time I spend looking at this damn screen instead of being with my own thoughts. It shouldn’t be this challenging. But it is. And that says tons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few years ago I wanted to do the same thing this author does—downgrade from smartphone to dumbphone—but to save money rather than to improve my contact with the outside world. My plan was to replace the smartphone with an iPad Mini, which I would use only on WiFi. Back then I shuttled every article I read from my RSS app (Reeder) to my read-it-later app (Pocket) and cached them offline, so I would rarely be without an offline time waster, to fill in those dull times in waiting rooms or on trains. I didn’t go through with the plan, though. I got caught up in smartphone fever along with everyone else in my office. It was an exciting time in the development of that technology—much more exciting than today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it is interesting and admirable to try to limit your smartphone use, and it is fun to read about someone’s experience with it. I &lt;em&gt;also&lt;/em&gt; think that this essay is the sort of thing my grandchildren will read in history class, perhaps on the whatever slab of glass and silicon they carry, and laugh at how silly we were to distrust the most transformative technology of our time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 09:41:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/i-quit-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/i-quit-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mjdescy.me/2018/04/30/premature-optimization/&quot;&gt;Premature Optimization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 23:15:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/blog-post-premature.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/05/01/blog-post-premature.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Introducing The New Yorker Crossword Puzzle</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/crossword/puzzles-dept/2018/04/30&quot;&gt;The New Yorker just launched a crossword puzzle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Most of our readers have e-mail addresses now, and the Web has given us the space to try new things—and to try old things again. In that spirit, we’re launching another crossword, online this time, and in the American style. It’ll be weekly, just like the magazine: a new one every Monday morning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a daily crossword puzzle player. I enjoy them, though I am not terribly good at them, because I love word games and have read that crosswords help keep your mind sharp into old age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New Yorker puzzle is a &lt;em&gt;tiny&lt;/em&gt; bit more challenging than I would like (as I said, I’m not a strong player), but I’m happy there’s another source of crossword puzzles (beyond the New York Times, which I also subscribe to) coming my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope they will someday move it into their iOS app. The scrolling behavior, which affects the on-page keyboard, is annoying on mobile.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 11:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/introducing-the-new.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/introducing-the-new.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Prolific Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo departs KGI Securities, likely to focus on companies other than Apple</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5mac.com/2018/04/30/prolific-apple-supply-chain-analyst-ming-chi-kuo-departs-kgi/&quot;&gt;Kuo’s departure&lt;/a&gt; comes hot off the heels of &lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5mac.com/2018/04/13/apple-memo-on-leaks-leaks/&quot;&gt;Apple’s recent “leaked” memo&lt;/a&gt; about leaking that threatened the leaky leaders who leak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Why has Ming-Chi Kuo, arguably one of the most popular technology analysts in the world, decided to move on? One possible reason is that his sources have done likewise, or perhaps have even been removed in light of Apple’s recent memo and strong stance against leaks — supply chain or otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wondered why myself, and figured that Apple has either threatened him, or his sources, with criminal lawsuits. I, for one, wouldn’t mind if Apple finally closed up all the leaks in its supply chain. While these leaks may benefit Apple investors,  they don’t really benefit Apple fans that much.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 09:49:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/prolific-apple-supply.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/prolific-apple-supply.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mjdescy.me/2018/04/30/my-slide-into-audiophile-territory-part-3/&quot;&gt;My slide into audiophile territory, Part 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 23:15:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/29/031528.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/031528.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Om Malik's Shinola Canfield headphone review</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Om Malik wrote &lt;a href=&quot;https://om.co/2018/04/29/shinolas-canfield-headphones/&quot;&gt;a thoughtful review&lt;/a&gt; of a rather high end headphone, the Shinola Canfield. He includes his philosophy on what makes good headphones, and states that you can find really good headphones between $200 and $500, which I wholeheartedly agree with. I especially enjoyed learning about which headphones he keeps around:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;At home, I listen to Focal Clear, probably the best and the most expensive headphones I will ever owned. I have no desire to either upgrade or change these phones. […]&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For conference calls and phone conversations, I use Apple AirPods. They aren’t my choice for music, but for watching videos on my iPad, they are more than adequate.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;For long-haul flights, I have a pair of beat-up Bose headphones that take AA batteries and are as low-tech as Bose can get. They sit in my luggage and will be there until Bose stops making the replacement ear pads. They are not great for music, but on a loud aircraft, they are just a way to mute everything.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love knowing that he and I have a similar lineup of headphones, and we split our time between them similarly: a top end headphone (except my top end are the Oppo PM-3, which cost a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; less than his Focal Clear); Apple AirPods for phone calls (I use them for calls, podcasts, and TV but almost never for music); and super old, now-crummy Bose for use on airplanes only.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 20:53:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/29/om-maliks-shinola.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/30/om-maliks-shinola.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I started using the Activity Digital face today. I never liked it before, but I’m trying to exercise more and it has been useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/99a8238f7f.jpg&quot; width=&quot;312&quot; height=&quot;313&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 23:44:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/28/i-started-using.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/29/i-started-using.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mjdescy.me/2018/04/28/swiftodo-development-notes-april-2018/&quot;&gt;SwiftoDo Development Notes, April 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 23:05:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/030506.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/28/030506.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>I miss Caesar salad</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that massive outbreaks of food borne illness are becoming more and more common. That &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/romaine-lettuce-e-coli-outbreak-worsens-98-people-now-sick-n869681&quot;&gt;our current, worsening outbreak&lt;/a&gt; is the &lt;em&gt;second&lt;/em&gt; E. Coli outbreak tied to my favorite type of lettuce in the past six months or so, and it is so virulent, is making me feel worried about our food system, and pessimistic about my country’s will to improve it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;An outbreak of E. coli food poisoning linked to romaine lettuce has widened and has now made at least 98 people sick, federal health officials said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;More than half have had to be hospitalized because the strain of E. coli causing this outbreak is an especially nasty one, the officials at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the Food and Drug Administration said.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;People in 22 states have reported E. coli infections linked to the outbreak, the CDC and FDA said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m no expert in this, but I feel like we have several problems in our food system that have, in the past few decades, started to compound in dangerous ways that we should have seen coming. Some of these problems include overcrowding of animals, overuse of antibiotics in livestock, and over-concentration in production and processing. When bad hygiene infects food, it’s worse now than it used to be. The bacteria are more resistant to antibiotics, and the food, and food borne illness, is distributed all across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another annoyance to me, as a someone who has eaten some raw eggs (usually in cookie dough or homemade eggnog) and rare meat over the years, is that I have &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; gotten a food borne illness from those activities. I have, however, gotten terribly ill several times from eating restaurant salads, probably due to unwashed hands or vegetables. There are menu warnings about undercooked meat in every restaurant I go to, but none about the danger of eating unwashed vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am impatiently awaiting the day I can eat Caesar salads again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 21:35:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/i-miss-caesar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/28/i-miss-caesar.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎬 &lt;a href=&quot;https://m.imdb.com/title/tt7451284/&quot;&gt;Batman Ninja&lt;/a&gt; is easily one of the weirdest movies I have seen—and that includes actual anime. I am still a bit puzzled why I watched it. I guess I’m a sucker for Batman and for animation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 19:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/batman-ninjahttpsmimdbcomtitlett-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/batman-ninjahttpsmimdbcomtitlett-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>📚 How We Got To Now</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading Steen Johnson’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/books/review/how-we-got-to-now-by-steven-johnson.html&quot;&gt;How We Got to Now: Six Innovations That Made the Modern World&lt;/a&gt;. It was a breezy and pleasurable read, full of interesting information. Johnson’s writing is clear, concise, and engaging throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a huge nerd who spent a lot of time in childhood perusing a science and technology encyclopedia, and a lot of time in my teens watching tech-related documentaries on Discovery and TLC (before those networks drifted to reality TV), I already knew a lot of the material. Still, it’s a wonderful read to anyone who loves the “history of ideas course” way of looking at disparate, seemingly unrelated things in everyday life, and drawing a through line that connects them all. Plus I learned new phrases that describe these unintended and intended technological and cultural developments—“hummingbird effects” and “the adjacent possible”—that I particularly like.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:03:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/how-we-got.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/how-we-got.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Finland Has Second Thoughts About Giving Free Money to Jobless People</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nyti.ms/2HpHmQE&quot;&gt;Finland is letting its yearlong experiment with Universal Basic Income expire&lt;/a&gt;. It turns out giving out tax money to people with no strings attached isn’t widely popular. What is interesting to me, a US citizen, is this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This may be the main reason that basic income has lost momentum in Finland: It is effectively redundant.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Health care is furnished by the state. University education is free. Jobless people draw generous unemployment benefits and have access to some of the most effective training programs on earth.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“In a sense,” said Mr. Hiilamo, the social policy professor, “Finland already has basic income.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I support Universal Basic Income. I think it would help the poor and would spur more people, like me, to start their own businesses. Of course, if we in the US had government provided healthcare, education, and job training programs, it might be enough to spur new business creation. I have the talent to start a consultancy, but the responsibility to pay for healthcare and my children’s education has always made me feel more secure with a normal, salaried position.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 09:08:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/finland-has-second.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/finland-has-second.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Amazon is increasing its Prime membership fee</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/amazon-doubles-its-profit---and-hikes-prime-membership-by-20/2018/04/26/31f5a14c-489a-11e8-827e-190efaf1f1ee_story.html?utm_term=.ff2227bbf7cb&quot;&gt;Amazon is increasing the price of Prime membership&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Amazon also said it will hike its Prime membership fee 20 percent to $119 a year for new members beginning May 11. Existing members who renew their Prime memberships will have to pay the new rate beginning June 16.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perversely, this news is making me want to buy &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; from them, to get a better value on shipping. I bet Amazon is expecting that response from some of their most loyal customers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 22:23:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/amazon-is-increasing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/amazon-is-increasing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I would pay good money to stream “Avengers: Infinity War” to my living room, so I could watch it after my kids go to bed. At home with Bluetooth headphones after 10 PM is basically the only way I can watch blockbusters these days.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 19:48:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/i-would-pay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/i-would-pay.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Mac apps are harder than iOS apps</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I agree with Matt Ronge’s article “&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/astro-hq/mac-apps-are-harder-than-ios-apps-614338e2e470&quot;&gt;Mac apps are harder than iOS apps&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I was surprised when a recent project brought me back to the Mac and I discovered how finicky Cocoa really is. I was particularly shocked because I always remembered Cocoa as a particularly nice set of APIs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my experience, a &lt;em&gt;big&lt;/em&gt; problem that Mr. Ronge does not mention is that there is very little information available online to help a macOS developer work through anything but the most basic situations. Sure, you can find some tutorials on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raywenderlich.com/category/macos&quot;&gt;raywenderlich.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCDg-YmnNehm3KB0BpytkUJg&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, but once you go beyond the basics, good information is hard to find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you search for “How do I do X? on iOS” you will likely find dozens or hundreds of hits, including numerous tutorials, open source libraries, and Stack Overflow questions. Conversely, you will be lucky to find one or two resources for the query “How do I do X? on macOS” (or OS X).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is understandable, because iOS is such a huge platform, but it is also quite frustrating, at least to a solo developer like me. If Apple creates &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-12-20/apple-is-said-to-have-plan-to-combine-iphone-ipad-and-mac-apps&quot;&gt;a new framework&lt;/a&gt; or shim layer to let us use iOS frameworks on macOS, I think it would make making Mac apps a lot easier for predominantly iOS-oriented developers like me..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 13:42:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/mac-apps-are.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/mac-apps-are.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>1Blocker X</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I picked up &lt;a href=&quot;https://1blocker.com/&quot;&gt;1Blocker X&lt;/a&gt; based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macstories.net/reviews/1blocker-x-for-ios-review/&quot;&gt;this review from John Voorhies on MacStores&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The first thing you will notice when you set up 1Blocker X on an iOS device is its 7 toggles in Safari’s Content Blocker section of the Settings app. It’s a bit of a head-scratcher at first until you realize that this is what allows 1Blocker X to expand beyond the confines of its predecessor.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;You see, iOS limits the number of blocking rules that can be implemented by an app to 50,000. That’s a lot of rules, but sadly not enough given the amount of junk on the Internet these days. As a result, it’s a limit that 1Blocker began to run into not long after it launched in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Finding a way around that hard limit required a rewrite of 1Blocker from the ground up. The result is 1Blocker X, an app with around three times as many blocking rules, room to grow, and enhanced flexibility for applying those rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I really needed to replace the content blocker I had been using, but it hadn’t been updated in a really long time, so I’m not sure it’s blocking rules are up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much of the work these things do is invisilble. It’s easy to see if ads are blocked, of course, but not so with trackers and malware, which I care more about. At home I &lt;em&gt;also&lt;/em&gt; block ads at the DNS level using &lt;a href=&quot;https://pi-hole.net/&quot;&gt;Pi-hole&lt;/a&gt;, running on an old Raspberry Pi. I heartily recommend setting up a Pi-hole (it’s easy; there are tutorials to follow). I miss having it when I’m out of the house, which is why a content blocker is helpful, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, 1Blocker X has been working just fine. I’ve noticed no decrease in speed from Safari, despite the crazy amount of blocking rules I have enabled.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:52:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/blocker-x.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/blocker-x.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m doing a type of work I haven’t done in about a year, and am feeling…rusty this morning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/im-doing-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/im-doing-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my life now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/81b387752b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:52:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/this-is-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/this-is-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got to be reminded today just how long VBA takes to run when used inside SQL Queries in Microsoft Access. I wish I could always use SQL Server, which is faster and better in every respect, but in my Company’s distributed environment, it’s always Access.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:30:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/i-got-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/i-got-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>AirPods batteries drain much faster on phone calls</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought my AirPods batteries were already aging out of their useful life span, due to quick draining on numerous hour long phone calls today and last week. It turns out, talk time is only “up to 2 hours”, while listening time (my main use case) is 2 1/2 times that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/shop/product/mmef2am/a/airpods&quot;&gt;Per Apple&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;AirPods (single charge): Up to 5 hours listening time,(2) Up to 2 hours talk time(5)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So…phew! I’m more worried about having to replace them after less than two years due to a battery issue than about shorter battery life on calls.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 10:56:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/23/airpods-batteries-drain.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/23/airpods-batteries-drain.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎧 I had a lot of fun testing out the V-Moda Crossfade 2 headphones last night. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/review/B06XX2TJSD/R1ZK34Q1MXP0I8?ref_=glimp_1rv_cl&quot;&gt;My review is on Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/b50778f79d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 08:58:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/22/i-had-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/22/i-had-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m eagerly awaiting my new &lt;a href=&quot;https://v-moda.com/products/crossfade2-wireless&quot;&gt;V-Moda Crossfade 2&lt;/a&gt;’s to be shipped. I want something that folds up, is durable, and sounds really good. I plan to drive them wired for serious music listening, and wireless for podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/5a37ea34be.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 09:55:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/20/im-eagerly-awaiting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/20/im-eagerly-awaiting.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 Frank Turner is—all at once—literate, angry, cynical, hurt, sad, and tender on &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/love-ire-song/317500956&quot;&gt;Love Ire &amp;amp; Song&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (Well, literate except for comma usage. 😀) Despite the negative emotions he expresses, his music is lively and compelling.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 16:25:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/frank-turner-isall.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/frank-turner-isall.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am coding VBA and ripping CDs like it’s the year 2000 today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 11:38:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/i-am-coding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/i-am-coding.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Git Tower vs. Atlassian SourceTree</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am enjoying using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.git-tower.com/mac/&quot;&gt;Tower&lt;/a&gt; over Atlassian SourceTree. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sourcetreeapp.com&quot;&gt;SourceTree&lt;/a&gt; has many, many features, and is free to use, but it has some puzzling bugs that never seem to get fixed. For example, it never deletes branches via Git Flow, no matter how many times I try to reconfigure it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tower is faster, works better, and has a clean UI that fits in on the Mac very well. When I emailed Tower support about something, they responded almost instantly. That sold it for me. When the Tower 3 beta expires, I will be purchasing a license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/108abb4d9a.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;339&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 21:54:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/18/git-tower-vs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/git-tower-vs.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Coding on my late 2013 15” MacBook Pro while watching MLB.TV at 60 FPS on the biggest TV in the house is a quite relaxing combo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 23:23:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/17/coding-on-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/18/coding-on-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 Taking a trip down memory lane with Guster’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/keep-it-together/1586602&quot;&gt;Keep It Together&lt;/a&gt; this evening, on my MacBook Pro and Oppo PM-3’s 🎧. Their records are cleanly produced, tightly written, and tastefully played. When I saw them &lt;em&gt;live&lt;/em&gt;, though, they absolutely shredded their way through their songs. They were freaking amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 22:22:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/taking-a-trip.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/17/taking-a-trip.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m starting to write the import routine I should have written when I first imported the data. Ain’t that always the way?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:05:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/im-starting-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/im-starting-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.beoplay.com/en/landingpages/beoplaym3#introducing&quot;&gt;BeoPlay M3&lt;/a&gt; speaker is a better fit in my kitchen than two feet away from me at my office desk. We got a lot of use out of it yesterday, Airplaying from iPhones and our Apple TV. It sounds better when played more loudly, in a larger room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/06393dee79.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 10:56:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/145601.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/145601.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m feeling pumped for work tomorrow, which is…12 hours too early. 🤷‍♂️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 19:34:57 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/im-feeling-pumped.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/im-feeling-pumped.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;📚 At long last, I have finished reading &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Team_of_Rivals&quot;&gt;Team of Rivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by Doris Kearns Goodwin. It (the last chapter and epilogue especially) has overwhelmed me with a sense of love and sadness, which is why it took me so long to read their whole thing. The book is a monumental achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 14:38:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/at-long-last.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/at-long-last.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am grateful that the grounds crew I hired cleaned up my yard today. The constant noise from their machines is really driving me nuts, though. They are at a house across the street now, so it has been seven hours of power tool noise for me today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 15:07:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-am-grateful.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-am-grateful.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I must be perverse or something, but one of my favorite apps on iOS is Apple’s Mail app. I tried several alternatives over the years, but Mail caught up to what I need from an email client a few years ago. I like how clean and simple it is, and rely on its unified inbox feature.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 09:26:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-must-be.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-must-be.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I excitedly signed up for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ulyssesapp.com/beta&quot;&gt;Ulysses 13 beta&lt;/a&gt; today. The feature I am most looking forward to is “improved code blocks with syntax highlighting”. If they provide Swift syntax highlighting in code blocks, I can finally use it for a &lt;em&gt;proper&lt;/em&gt; developer’s log.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 22:39:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/i-excitedly-signed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-excitedly-signed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I deactivated by Facebook account today. I can’t muster up the gumption to delete it, and don’t know why. But it’s a start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/5e23a06a8b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;203&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 16:10:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/i-deactivated-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/i-deactivated-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m trying to catch up to current Red Sox games on MLB At Bat. I’m still a few days behind. It’s a losing battle every baseball season, because the games are so long.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 09:22:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/132245.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/132245.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Somehow my simple feature update in my app ballooned to a 38-file refactor. 😳 I’m in a better position now for a number of additional little updates now, thanks to the the extra work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 20:53:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/11/somehow-my-simple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/somehow-my-simple.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The spring cleanup landscaping quotes I got this week have a range of $1,400 for the same work. It really pays to shop around, I guess.  Fortunately, my current lawnmowing company put in the lowest quote and can do the work the soonest.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 11:17:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/11/the-spring-cleanup.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/11/the-spring-cleanup.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
