<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Descy</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/mjdescy&quot;&gt;@mjdescy on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:04:22 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:04:22 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 The Grammy Awards are really, really stupid. Still, you should &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/by-the-way-i-forgive-you/1310052885&quot;&gt;listen to some Brandi Carlile&lt;/a&gt;, who &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2018/12/07/674493226/kendrick-lamar-female-nominees-lead-major-grammy-nominations&quot;&gt;was nominated for a bunch of them today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:03:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/07/the-grammy-awards.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/07/the-grammy-awards.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cool. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macstories.net/news/electrocardiogram-app-and-irregular-heart-rhythm-notifications-available-today/&quot;&gt;The new heart monitoring and ECG features are hitting the Apple Watch Series 4 today.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:19:59 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/06/cool-the-new.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/06/cool-the-new.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Siri Shortcuts is suggesting I call our favorite pizza place right now. Things have gone horribly awry with us, diet wise. 😂&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:44:04 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/05/siri-shortcuts-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/05/siri-shortcuts-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My wife and I paid off our newer car today, which feels great after 3 years of monthly payments. Of course, I need to replace our older car (which is 15 years old and on its last legs) later this month, so car payments will continue unabated.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/05/211700.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/05/211700.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The best news I will hear today came pretty early: &lt;a href=&quot;https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/the-good-place-renewed-season-4-nbc-1203032958/&quot;&gt;“The Good Place” Renewed for Season 4 at NYC&lt;/a&gt;. I should go back to bed now (or at least shut off my connection to the Internet) before things get worse.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:26:58 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/05/the-best-news.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/05/the-best-news.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I envy people whose voicemail boxes are full.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:31:30 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/03/i-envy-people.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/03/i-envy-people.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>🎵 River of Dreams</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m not a &lt;em&gt;huge&lt;/em&gt; Billy Joel fan, though I do have all his albums and respect him as an artist. I wish he had written another album after &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/river-of-dreams/158619540&quot;&gt;River of Dreams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, which I am listening to again today. I think that, as a maker of &lt;em&gt;albums&lt;/em&gt;, rather than singles, he hit his stride with &lt;em&gt;Storm Front&lt;/em&gt; and that, &lt;em&gt;as an album&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;River of Dreams&lt;/em&gt; is his best. His earlier albums have higher highs and lower lows, and don’t hold together as well, in my opinion. I prefer picking through his excellent &lt;em&gt;Greatest Hits&lt;/em&gt; collections rather than revisit the albums the songs come from.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:11:56 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/03/river-of-dreams.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/03/river-of-dreams.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>My home cooking tip to add a vegetable and a sauce to stovetop chicken breasts</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my simple kitchen techniques to spruce up skinless, boneless chicken breasts is to throw a can of beans (cannellini or garbanzo) and some chicken broth on them, after searing the first side. I then cover them and simmer the chicken (typically in the oven) until it is done. I usually throw in some flour at the end, after taking the chicken out, to make a thick and creamy sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://micro.mjdescy.me/uploads/2018/d60e69ad5b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 14:09:22 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/02/my-home-cooking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/02/my-home-cooking.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I bought my wife the iPhone XR tonight at the Apple Store. She and I had fun setting it up. If it came out before the X, I think people would not have gone so crazy about the X.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 21:56:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/12/01/i-bought-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/02/i-bought-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>My Micro 4/3 Camera is all kitted out</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have just about every accessory I would imagine I would need for my (still) new Olympus OM-D EM10 Mark III camera, and all of them, except for the little carrying case it came with and my AmazonBasics tripod, fit into this little box. I never expected to buy so many lenses in such a short time (over a 4-month period). I was having so much fun shooting photos and expanding my camera’s versatility. I tracked lens prices closely for months and bought each lens on a price dip; all in all I saved hundreds of dollars, compared to what it would have cost if I bought everything up front. Still, I spent way too much money this year on the camera; but at least I’m almost done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To keep everything neat and tidy, rather than lumped together in a little box, I think want some kind of padded, hardshell case for everything (such as a Pelican case). I’m not sure it’s worth the expense, though, because I don’t think I would ever take it out of the house. I would continue to use the little case that came with the camera, which I love for its small size. It easily fits the camera and an extra lens or an external flash unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I sort the case situation out, I will be done with camera spending…at least for a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://micro.mjdescy.me/uploads/2018/742f860a2d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:07:13 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/30/my-micro-camera.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/12/01/my-micro-camera.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Kodex: An iOS code/text editor I just discovered</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just discovered a versatile code (and text) editor for iOS called &lt;a href=&quot;https://kodex.app&quot;&gt;Kodex&lt;/a&gt;. It is a free app with some pretty cool features:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;tight integration with the Files app&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;syntax highlighting for numerous languages (including Markdown)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;multiple tabbed interface&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a large assortment of hardware keyboard shortcuts, which you can customize the key bindings for&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;multiple cursor support (it’s more rudimentary than Sublime Text’s, which works with “next word” selection and the mouse, but it’s a desktop-only app)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;find/replace&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;find/replace with regEx&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;document minimap&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a large assortment of themes and color schemes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As nice as iOS is for text editing, especially if you have a hardware keyboard, it is hard to not see just how rudimentary most of its text editors are. There certainly is nothing like BBEdit or Sublime Text available on the platform (though Kodex is definitely aiming at Sublime Text, in its functionality).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t even think of any iOS text editor, other than Kodex (which I just discovered), that supports working with documents in multiple tabs.  (Apple should really just make a Safari-like tab bar controller a standard component. I know I would use it in my apps.) Even features that are common on the desktop, like find and replace, have only become common on iOS in the past year or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best text editors on the platform (such as Drafts) are made with MarkDown and automation in mind, which is cool. But they are simplistic compared to what is available on the desktop. I would love it if something as fast and versatile as Sublime Text was released on iOS. I would probably pay a lot of money for it, too.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:22:24 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/29/kodex-an-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/30/kodex-an-ios.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m fixing minor UI bugs in one of my apps this week. I’m doing necessary work, but the &lt;em&gt;big, bad bug&lt;/em&gt; that I rarely see, but know exists, is still out there, somewhere, &lt;em&gt;lurking&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:13:42 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/29/im-fixing-minor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/30/im-fixing-minor.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Removing Dropbox, and Finding a Replacement for Editorial on iOS</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m working on retiring Dropbox from all my systems. For personal files, I am all in on iCloud. For work files, which I want separate, I am going to use OneDrive (which is IT-supported). I am stuck, though, trying to figure out what text (and Markdown) editor I can use on iOS that will be acceptable to me. Pretext crashes on long files, but is otherwise OK. 1Writer is OK, but had trouble opening some of my files, and I don’t like its floating buttons. There are so many decent Dropbox-enabled text editors on iOS, but very few that integrate well with the Files app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:31:53 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/28/removing-dropbox-and.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/28/removing-dropbox-and.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Am I the only one who thinks that Facebook’s commercials for its video chat gadget, the Portal, are in incredibly poor taste? Putting aside the obvious problem that putting a video camera controlled by Facebook in your home is a terrible idea on numerous levels, the jokey video calls they depict are so &lt;em&gt;mean spirited&lt;/em&gt; that it actually makes me sad to see them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:57:45 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/26/135745.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/26/135745.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There are actually some good Black Friday deals on Master &amp;amp; Dynamics and Bose QC 35 headphones 🎧, and some KEF speakers 🔉🔉 I had my eye on. Of course, I already spent my “gifts to myself” money this year. &lt;a href=&quot;https://thewirecutter.com/deals/black-friday/&quot;&gt;Wirecutter has a great list of deals&lt;/a&gt;. 💸&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 09:34:25 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/23/there-are-actually.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/23/there-are-actually.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is my obligatory Thanksgiving turkey photo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://micro.mjdescy.me/uploads/2018/34d644cc2d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 19:23:05 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/22/here-is-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/23/here-is-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just got up. Time to start cooking!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:12:46 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/22/131246.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/22/131246.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The NY style crumb cake I baked this evening looks so amateurish that I dubbed it “baby’s first cake”. 😅&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:29:41 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/21/the-ny-style.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/22/the-ny-style.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think I need Apple’s “Screen Time” feature only for &lt;em&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild&lt;/em&gt; (which of course runs on the Nintendo Switch).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 08:46:42 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/21/134642.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/21/134642.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of my cooking and cleaning plans today were derailed when my kitchen sink detached from the granite countertop. I was soaking oven racks in scalding hot water, which I do every year around this time, but this time the weight and the heat were too much. The sink’s seaI failed, and the sink dropped about an inch on one side. I had to bail gallons of hot water out with a bowl. Luckily, I was able to get it repaired about an hour later, but I can’t use the sink again until sometime tomorrow. At least this didn’t happen to me on Thanksgiving!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://micro.mjdescy.me/uploads/2018/c80dc7fc6b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:26:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/20/most-of-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/20/most-of-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I have enjoyed Regina Spektor’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/remember-us-to-life/1132797621&quot;&gt;Remember Us To Life&lt;/a&gt; for the past two years. Her evocative lyrics, expressive voice, and theatrical arrangements make this collection of songs loom large in my imagination.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:54:21 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/19/i-have-enjoyed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/19/i-have-enjoyed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am working only one day this week. I wish every week was like this one!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:40:53 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/19/i-am-working.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/19/i-am-working.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a nice lunch with my family, I will say that I am thankful for the little Italian market and deli nearby that sells yummy foods.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 13:11:31 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/17/after-a-nice.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/17/after-a-nice.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t really like how Mastodon posts are now in the auto-generated Discover sections for things like music and specific sports. I just want to see Micro.blog posts in Discover.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 16:43:43 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/16/i-dont-really.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/16/i-dont-really.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am happy that I was able to cook homemade chicken soup for my family this evening.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 18:52:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/15/235255.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/15/235255.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I can’t believe we got a couple inches of snow on the ground today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 18:09:19 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/15/i-cant-believe.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/15/i-cant-believe.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am disappointed in the current slate of Broadway musicals. I thought last year was particularly weak, but this year is worse. I am only an infrequent Broadway theater goer, do to the ticket prices, but I listen to a lot of cast recordings. Nothing is grabbing my attention now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 09:21:37 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/15/i-am-disappointed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/15/i-am-disappointed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do any Micro.bloggers have any suggestions for a good iOS guided meditation app for beginners? There are so many to choose from.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 09:13:11 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/14/do-any-microbloggers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/14/do-any-microbloggers.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m happy that the Accidental Tech Podcast hosts got invited to the Apple Mac and iPad event, and that &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/marco&quot;&gt;@marco&lt;/a&gt; got a couple of review units, too. I have enjoyed ATP’s last two episodes all the more because of it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:23:07 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/09/im-happy-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/09/im-happy-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I’m listening to a bunch of different versions of what is probably the greatest Bossa nova song ever: “&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/%C3%A1guas-de-marco/263743484?i=263743529&quot;&gt;Aguas de Marco&lt;/a&gt;”/”&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/the-waters-of-march/152819588?i=152819611&quot;&gt;Waters of March&lt;/a&gt;”. It’s lovely and hypnotic.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 10:56:43 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/07/im-listening-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/07/im-listening-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Chrome (on Windows 10) does not take &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; long to load, but it takes long enough for me to forget why I launched it by the time it opens.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 14:54:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/06/chrome-on-windows.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/06/chrome-on-windows.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I voted!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 14:51:34 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/06/i-voted.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/06/i-voted.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My favorite line from &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/gruber&quot;&gt;@gruber&lt;/a&gt;’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://daringfireball.net/2018/11/the_2018_retina_macbook_air&quot;&gt;2018 MacBook Air review&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Esc key works perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am so relieved.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/06/my-favorite-line.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/06/my-favorite-line.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I thought to myself this morning: “Why don’t I just play &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/0d8aVzQY4Zo&quot;&gt;all my songs on shuffle&lt;/a&gt;?”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 09:47:28 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/06/i-thought-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/06/i-thought-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My employer is changing its email retention policy to discourage employees from keeping email &lt;em&gt;forever&lt;/em&gt;, and focusing on its use as a communication tool rather than an historical archive. I have been waiting for 20 years for such a thing to occur.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:43:37 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/06/my-employer-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/06/my-employer-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am excited to go vote today. My wife and I made a voting plan and everything. Thankfully it is not that hard for us to vote where we live.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 07:28:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/06/122839.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/06/122839.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🕹 I have been playing a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of Breath of the Wild and Super Mario Odyssey the past couple weeks. I am very glad I bought them. It’s good to have escapist fun for a change.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 15:17:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/05/201723.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/05/201723.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I bought a “fast” lens for my micro 4/3 camera to take pictures of my kids indoors, where the light is not good. I have gotten some great shots, but I have concluded, after about a month of shooting, that what I really need is a TTL flash that I can bounce off the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:56:41 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/05/i-bought-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/05/i-bought-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;No one told my kids that Daylight Saving Time has ended. 😴&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 07:55:32 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/04/no-one-told.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/04/no-one-told.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://votesaveamerica.com/ballot&quot;&gt;VoteSaveAmerica’s voting guide&lt;/a&gt; is very well done. I was able to quickly learn about the candidates and the ballot measures that will be on my actual ballot on November 6.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 20:31:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/01/votesaveamericas-voting-guide.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/02/votesaveamericas-voting-guide.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have not been looking at polls, because I don’t want to drive myself crazy, but I am really nervous about voter turnout for next week’s midterm election. I have a vague dread that Democrats will, once again, not vote in large enough numbers to help un-f*** this country.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 20:25:17 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/11/01/002517.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/02/002517.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Halloween with the wife and kids was fun. It was unusually warm and we didn’t have many trick-or-treaters in our neighborhood this year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 20:16:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/31/halloween-with-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/11/01/halloween-with-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/25/realestate/a-broadway-actor-has-a-heart-to-heart-about-life-and-laundry.html&quot;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt;, about an actor’s family finding an apartment as they move to NYC, is kind of depressing. It’s unreasonably expensive to live in the city. If I were in his position, I would probably try to live outside the city a little ways.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 19:43:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/30/234340.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/30/234340.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Oh, now Lana Del Ray and Jack Antonoff are on stage. This is the best Apple event in many years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 11:22:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/30/oh-now-lana.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/30/oh-now-lana.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is anyone else hearing the distorted Halloween echo whenever Tim Cook is speaking at the Apple iPad Pro event?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 10:05:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/30/is-anyone-else.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/30/is-anyone-else.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 How have I never listened to “&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Last_Waltz&quot;&gt;The Last Waltz&lt;/a&gt;” before? I guess because I thought it would be sad to listen to the last concert by a band (&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Band&quot;&gt;The Band&lt;/a&gt;) I loved. &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/the-last-waltz/705585893&quot;&gt;It isn’t sad at all.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 09:40:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/30/how-have-i.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/30/how-have-i.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Both my kids fell in love with the book, song, and music video (!) for &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicka_Chicka_Boom_Boom&quot;&gt;Chicka Chicka Boom Boom&lt;/a&gt; this month. It’s cute, but a little weird.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:56:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/30/both-my-kids.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/30/both-my-kids.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Fall&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://micro.mjdescy.me/uploads/2018/18f0b362d6.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 19:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/29/fall.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/29/fall.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I do not listen to nearly enough Neko Case. For the first time in forever, I just spun up her 2002 album, &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/blacklisted/264606873&quot;&gt;Blacklisted&lt;/a&gt;, with its electric lead track: “Things that Scare Me”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 15:36:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/29/i-do-not.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/29/i-do-not.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I’m trying to listen to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/pretty-woman-the-musical-original-broadway-cast-recording/1423345741&quot;&gt;Original Broadway Cast recording of “Pretty Woman: the Musical”&lt;/a&gt; and it is hard to get through. So boring, so trite. The cast is good, though. Andy Karl, in particular, needs to find a role in a show not based on a movie for a change.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:13:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://micro.mjdescy.me/2018/10/29/151337.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/10/29/151337.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
