<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Descy</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/mjdescy&quot;&gt;@mjdescy on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 23:05:14 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 23:05:14 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Blog post: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mjdescy.me/2018/04/28/swiftodo-development-notes-april-2018/&quot;&gt;SwiftoDo Development Notes, April 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 23:05:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/030506.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/28/030506.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>I miss Caesar salad</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that massive outbreaks of food borne illness are becoming more and more common. That &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/romaine-lettuce-e-coli-outbreak-worsens-98-people-now-sick-n869681&quot;&gt;our current, worsening outbreak&lt;/a&gt; is the &lt;em&gt;second&lt;/em&gt; E. Coli outbreak tied to my favorite type of lettuce in the past six months or so, and it is so virulent, is making me feel worried about our food system, and pessimistic about my country’s will to improve it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;An outbreak of E. coli food poisoning linked to romaine lettuce has widened and has now made at least 98 people sick, federal health officials said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;More than half have had to be hospitalized because the strain of E. coli causing this outbreak is an especially nasty one, the officials at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the Food and Drug Administration said.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;People in 22 states have reported E. coli infections linked to the outbreak, the CDC and FDA said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m no expert in this, but I feel like we have several problems in our food system that have, in the past few decades, started to compound in dangerous ways that we should have seen coming. Some of these problems include overcrowding of animals, overuse of antibiotics in livestock, and over-concentration in production and processing. When bad hygiene infects food, it’s worse now than it used to be. The bacteria are more resistant to antibiotics, and the food, and food borne illness, is distributed all across the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another annoyance to me, as a someone who has eaten some raw eggs (usually in cookie dough or homemade eggnog) and rare meat over the years, is that I have &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; gotten a food borne illness from those activities. I have, however, gotten terribly ill several times from eating restaurant salads, probably due to unwashed hands or vegetables. There are menu warnings about undercooked meat in every restaurant I go to, but none about the danger of eating unwashed vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am impatiently awaiting the day I can eat Caesar salads again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 21:35:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/i-miss-caesar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/28/i-miss-caesar.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎬 &lt;a href=&quot;https://m.imdb.com/title/tt7451284/&quot;&gt;Batman Ninja&lt;/a&gt; is easily one of the weirdest movies I have seen—and that includes actual anime. I am still a bit puzzled why I watched it. I guess I’m a sucker for Batman and for animation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 19:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/batman-ninjahttpsmimdbcomtitlett-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/batman-ninjahttpsmimdbcomtitlett-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>📚 How We Got To Now</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading Steen Johnson’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2014/12/28/books/review/how-we-got-to-now-by-steven-johnson.html&quot;&gt;How We Got to Now: Six Innovations That Made the Modern World&lt;/a&gt;. It was a breezy and pleasurable read, full of interesting information. Johnson’s writing is clear, concise, and engaging throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a huge nerd who spent a lot of time in childhood perusing a science and technology encyclopedia, and a lot of time in my teens watching tech-related documentaries on Discovery and TLC (before those networks drifted to reality TV), I already knew a lot of the material. Still, it’s a wonderful read to anyone who loves the “history of ideas course” way of looking at disparate, seemingly unrelated things in everyday life, and drawing a through line that connects them all. Plus I learned new phrases that describe these unintended and intended technological and cultural developments—“hummingbird effects” and “the adjacent possible”—that I particularly like.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:03:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/how-we-got.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/how-we-got.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Finland Has Second Thoughts About Giving Free Money to Jobless People</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nyti.ms/2HpHmQE&quot;&gt;Finland is letting its yearlong experiment with Universal Basic Income expire&lt;/a&gt;. It turns out giving out tax money to people with no strings attached isn’t widely popular. What is interesting to me, a US citizen, is this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This may be the main reason that basic income has lost momentum in Finland: It is effectively redundant.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Health care is furnished by the state. University education is free. Jobless people draw generous unemployment benefits and have access to some of the most effective training programs on earth.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;“In a sense,” said Mr. Hiilamo, the social policy professor, “Finland already has basic income.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I support Universal Basic Income. I think it would help the poor and would spur more people, like me, to start their own businesses. Of course, if we in the US had government provided healthcare, education, and job training programs, it might be enough to spur new business creation. I have the talent to start a consultancy, but the responsibility to pay for healthcare and my children’s education has always made me feel more secure with a normal, salaried position.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 09:08:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/finland-has-second.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/finland-has-second.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Amazon is increasing its Prime membership fee</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/amazon-doubles-its-profit---and-hikes-prime-membership-by-20/2018/04/26/31f5a14c-489a-11e8-827e-190efaf1f1ee_story.html?utm_term=.ff2227bbf7cb&quot;&gt;Amazon is increasing the price of Prime membership&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Amazon also said it will hike its Prime membership fee 20 percent to $119 a year for new members beginning May 11. Existing members who renew their Prime memberships will have to pay the new rate beginning June 16.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perversely, this news is making me want to buy &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; from them, to get a better value on shipping. I bet Amazon is expecting that response from some of their most loyal customers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 22:23:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/amazon-is-increasing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/27/amazon-is-increasing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I would pay good money to stream “Avengers: Infinity War” to my living room, so I could watch it after my kids go to bed. At home with Bluetooth headphones after 10 PM is basically the only way I can watch blockbusters these days.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 19:48:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/i-would-pay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/i-would-pay.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Mac apps are harder than iOS apps</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I agree with Matt Ronge’s article “&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/astro-hq/mac-apps-are-harder-than-ios-apps-614338e2e470&quot;&gt;Mac apps are harder than iOS apps&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I was surprised when a recent project brought me back to the Mac and I discovered how finicky Cocoa really is. I was particularly shocked because I always remembered Cocoa as a particularly nice set of APIs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my experience, a &lt;em&gt;big&lt;/em&gt; problem that Mr. Ronge does not mention is that there is very little information available online to help a macOS developer work through anything but the most basic situations. Sure, you can find some tutorials on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raywenderlich.com/category/macos&quot;&gt;raywenderlich.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCDg-YmnNehm3KB0BpytkUJg&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, but once you go beyond the basics, good information is hard to find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you search for “How do I do X? on iOS” you will likely find dozens or hundreds of hits, including numerous tutorials, open source libraries, and Stack Overflow questions. Conversely, you will be lucky to find one or two resources for the query “How do I do X? on macOS” (or OS X).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is understandable, because iOS is such a huge platform, but it is also quite frustrating, at least to a solo developer like me. If Apple creates &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-12-20/apple-is-said-to-have-plan-to-combine-iphone-ipad-and-mac-apps&quot;&gt;a new framework&lt;/a&gt; or shim layer to let us use iOS frameworks on macOS, I think it would make making Mac apps a lot easier for predominantly iOS-oriented developers like me..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 13:42:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/mac-apps-are.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/mac-apps-are.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>1Blocker X</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I picked up &lt;a href=&quot;https://1blocker.com/&quot;&gt;1Blocker X&lt;/a&gt; based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macstories.net/reviews/1blocker-x-for-ios-review/&quot;&gt;this review from John Voorhies on MacStores&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The first thing you will notice when you set up 1Blocker X on an iOS device is its 7 toggles in Safari’s Content Blocker section of the Settings app. It’s a bit of a head-scratcher at first until you realize that this is what allows 1Blocker X to expand beyond the confines of its predecessor.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;You see, iOS limits the number of blocking rules that can be implemented by an app to 50,000. That’s a lot of rules, but sadly not enough given the amount of junk on the Internet these days. As a result, it’s a limit that 1Blocker began to run into not long after it launched in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Finding a way around that hard limit required a rewrite of 1Blocker from the ground up. The result is 1Blocker X, an app with around three times as many blocking rules, room to grow, and enhanced flexibility for applying those rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I really needed to replace the content blocker I had been using, but it hadn’t been updated in a really long time, so I’m not sure it’s blocking rules are up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much of the work these things do is invisilble. It’s easy to see if ads are blocked, of course, but not so with trackers and malware, which I care more about. At home I &lt;em&gt;also&lt;/em&gt; block ads at the DNS level using &lt;a href=&quot;https://pi-hole.net/&quot;&gt;Pi-hole&lt;/a&gt;, running on an old Raspberry Pi. I heartily recommend setting up a Pi-hole (it’s easy; there are tutorials to follow). I miss having it when I’m out of the house, which is why a content blocker is helpful, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, 1Blocker X has been working just fine. I’ve noticed no decrease in speed from Safari, despite the crazy amount of blocking rules I have enabled.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:52:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/blocker-x.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/blocker-x.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m doing a type of work I haven’t done in about a year, and am feeling…rusty this morning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/im-doing-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/26/im-doing-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my life now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/81b387752b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:52:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/this-is-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/this-is-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got to be reminded today just how long VBA takes to run when used inside SQL Queries in Microsoft Access. I wish I could always use SQL Server, which is faster and better in every respect, but in my Company’s distributed environment, it’s always Access.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 14:30:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/i-got-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/24/i-got-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>AirPods batteries drain much faster on phone calls</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought my AirPods batteries were already aging out of their useful life span, due to quick draining on numerous hour long phone calls today and last week. It turns out, talk time is only “up to 2 hours”, while listening time (my main use case) is 2 1/2 times that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/shop/product/mmef2am/a/airpods&quot;&gt;Per Apple&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;AirPods (single charge): Up to 5 hours listening time,(2) Up to 2 hours talk time(5)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So…phew! I’m more worried about having to replace them after less than two years due to a battery issue than about shorter battery life on calls.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 10:56:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/23/airpods-batteries-drain.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/23/airpods-batteries-drain.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎧 I had a lot of fun testing out the V-Moda Crossfade 2 headphones last night. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/review/B06XX2TJSD/R1ZK34Q1MXP0I8?ref_=glimp_1rv_cl&quot;&gt;My review is on Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/b50778f79d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 08:58:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/22/i-had-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/22/i-had-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m eagerly awaiting my new &lt;a href=&quot;https://v-moda.com/products/crossfade2-wireless&quot;&gt;V-Moda Crossfade 2&lt;/a&gt;’s to be shipped. I want something that folds up, is durable, and sounds really good. I plan to drive them wired for serious music listening, and wireless for podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/5a37ea34be.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 09:55:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/20/im-eagerly-awaiting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/20/im-eagerly-awaiting.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 Frank Turner is—all at once—literate, angry, cynical, hurt, sad, and tender on &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/love-ire-song/317500956&quot;&gt;Love Ire &amp;amp; Song&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (Well, literate except for comma usage. 😀) Despite the negative emotions he expresses, his music is lively and compelling.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 16:25:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/frank-turner-isall.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/frank-turner-isall.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am coding VBA and ripping CDs like it’s the year 2000 today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 11:38:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/i-am-coding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/i-am-coding.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Git Tower vs. Atlassian SourceTree</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am enjoying using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.git-tower.com/mac/&quot;&gt;Tower&lt;/a&gt; over Atlassian SourceTree. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sourcetreeapp.com&quot;&gt;SourceTree&lt;/a&gt; has many, many features, and is free to use, but it has some puzzling bugs that never seem to get fixed. For example, it never deletes branches via Git Flow, no matter how many times I try to reconfigure it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tower is faster, works better, and has a clean UI that fits in on the Mac very well. When I emailed Tower support about something, they responded almost instantly. That sold it for me. When the Tower 3 beta expires, I will be purchasing a license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/108abb4d9a.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;339&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 21:54:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/18/git-tower-vs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/19/git-tower-vs.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Coding on my late 2013 15” MacBook Pro while watching MLB.TV at 60 FPS on the biggest TV in the house is a quite relaxing combo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 23:23:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/17/coding-on-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/18/coding-on-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 Taking a trip down memory lane with Guster’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/keep-it-together/1586602&quot;&gt;Keep It Together&lt;/a&gt; this evening, on my MacBook Pro and Oppo PM-3’s 🎧. Their records are cleanly produced, tightly written, and tastefully played. When I saw them &lt;em&gt;live&lt;/em&gt;, though, they absolutely shredded their way through their songs. They were freaking amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 22:22:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/taking-a-trip.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/17/taking-a-trip.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m starting to write the import routine I should have written when I first imported the data. Ain’t that always the way?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:05:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/im-starting-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/im-starting-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.beoplay.com/en/landingpages/beoplaym3#introducing&quot;&gt;BeoPlay M3&lt;/a&gt; speaker is a better fit in my kitchen than two feet away from me at my office desk. We got a lot of use out of it yesterday, Airplaying from iPhones and our Apple TV. It sounds better when played more loudly, in a larger room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/06393dee79.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 10:56:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/145601.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/16/145601.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m feeling pumped for work tomorrow, which is…12 hours too early. 🤷‍♂️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 19:34:57 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/im-feeling-pumped.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/im-feeling-pumped.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;📚 At long last, I have finished reading &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Team_of_Rivals&quot;&gt;Team of Rivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by Doris Kearns Goodwin. It (the last chapter and epilogue especially) has overwhelmed me with a sense of love and sadness, which is why it took me so long to read their whole thing. The book is a monumental achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 14:38:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/at-long-last.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/15/at-long-last.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am grateful that the grounds crew I hired cleaned up my yard today. The constant noise from their machines is really driving me nuts, though. They are at a house across the street now, so it has been seven hours of power tool noise for me today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 15:07:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-am-grateful.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-am-grateful.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I must be perverse or something, but one of my favorite apps on iOS is Apple’s Mail app. I tried several alternatives over the years, but Mail caught up to what I need from an email client a few years ago. I like how clean and simple it is, and rely on its unified inbox feature.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 09:26:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-must-be.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-must-be.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I excitedly signed up for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://ulyssesapp.com/beta&quot;&gt;Ulysses 13 beta&lt;/a&gt; today. The feature I am most looking forward to is “improved code blocks with syntax highlighting”. If they provide Swift syntax highlighting in code blocks, I can finally use it for a &lt;em&gt;proper&lt;/em&gt; developer’s log.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 22:39:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/i-excitedly-signed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/13/i-excitedly-signed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I deactivated by Facebook account today. I can’t muster up the gumption to delete it, and don’t know why. But it’s a start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/5e23a06a8b.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;203&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 16:10:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/i-deactivated-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/i-deactivated-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m trying to catch up to current Red Sox games on MLB At Bat. I’m still a few days behind. It’s a losing battle every baseball season, because the games are so long.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 09:22:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/132245.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/132245.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Somehow my simple feature update in my app ballooned to a 38-file refactor. 😳 I’m in a better position now for a number of additional little updates now, thanks to the the extra work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 20:53:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/11/somehow-my-simple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/12/somehow-my-simple.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The spring cleanup landscaping quotes I got this week have a range of $1,400 for the same work. It really pays to shop around, I guess.  Fortunately, my current lawnmowing company put in the lowest quote and can do the work the soonest.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 11:17:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/11/the-spring-cleanup.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/11/the-spring-cleanup.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 “&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/space-gun/1342390133&quot;&gt;Space Gun&lt;/a&gt;” by Guided by Voices sounds just as good and just as vital as their old stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 15:40:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/10/space-gunhttpsitunesapplecomusalbumspacegun-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/10/space-gunhttpsitunesapplecomusalbumspacegun-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My current background task, while I work, is secure erasing a bunch of old, small, unneeded hard drives, to prepare them for recycling. I wish I had encrypted them, to avoid all the wait time ahead of me, but that wasn’t really an option back when I used them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/2f3e68fc11.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 08:54:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/10/my-current-background.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/10/my-current-background.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you can program on your hobby projects after work, but sometimes you have to clean house. April is a clean-house kind of month for me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 20:49:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/sometimes-you-can.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/10/sometimes-you-can.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I’m really digging Bleachers’ “&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/gone-now/1225759934&quot;&gt;Gone Now&lt;/a&gt;” right now. I like everything that Jack Antonoff does.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 16:42:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/im-really-digging.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/im-really-digging.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m getting back in the swing of things at work now. I’m in the groove. Here’s to a productive week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 14:07:57 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/im-getting-back.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/im-getting-back.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://swiftodoapp.com&quot;&gt;SwiftoDo 2.11.2&lt;/a&gt; is now available &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/swiftodo-task-list-for-todo.txt/id1073798440?ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;in the App Store&lt;/a&gt;. No new features this time, but the code has been updated to Swift 4.1.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 09:28:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/132809.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/09/132809.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is a rebuilding day after 2 days in NYC. The city is fun but we are all happy to be back at home.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 12:04:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/08/today-is-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/08/today-is-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was not happy to learn today that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.oppodigital.com/farewell.aspx&quot;&gt;OPPO Digital is going out of business&lt;/a&gt;. They make my absolute favorite headphones, the OPPO PM-3. 🎧😥&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 18:54:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/04/225406.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/04/225406.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It may be too soon to tell, but I’m afraid &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/digby-forever/id1143705385?mt=8&quot;&gt;Digby Forever&lt;/a&gt; has ruined my life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 20:27:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/03/it-may-be.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/04/it-may-be.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;🎵 I re-listened to The Decemberists’ &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/ill-be-your-girl/1333620066&quot;&gt;I’ll Be Your Girl&lt;/a&gt; today, and was surprised that all the songs sounded like I had always known them. I enjoyed the album a lot more today than on my first listen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 16:42:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/03/i-relistened-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/03/i-relistened-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know you can filter Excel spreadsheet columns by &lt;em&gt;color&lt;/em&gt;? &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.office.com/en-us/article/filter-data-in-a-range-or-table-01832226-31b5-4568-8806-38c37dcc180e&quot;&gt;You sure can&lt;/a&gt;! It came in handy today.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 15:00:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/03/did-you-know.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/03/did-you-know.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Someone just tried to hack into my Apple account. Scary! I’m glad I have two factor authentication turned on. I got notifications on all my devices and quickly changed my password for the first time in a couple years. I wonder what happened.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 21:23:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/01/someone-just-tried.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/02/someone-just-tried.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our plans today include Easter egg dying and a Passover Seder with family. I prefer brisket to Easter ham any day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 11:53:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/01/our-plans-today.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/04/01/our-plans-today.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re going to Six Flags Great Adventure today on the first warm-ish day of spring. I’m excited. We’ll see how it is. I’ve never gone there before.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 10:19:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/31/were-going-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/31/were-going-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My Mac came back from the stalled OS update, but I decided to nuke the hard drive and reinstall macOS anyway. Too many little things have been broken lately. It’s the first time I have done so on this machine ever. I’ve had it almost 5 years. 🤞&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://mjdescy.micro.blog/uploads/2018/42e19f53ae.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 15:18:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/my-mac-came.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/my-mac-came.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://swiftodoapp.com&quot;&gt;SwiftoDo 2.11.1&lt;/a&gt; is now available &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/swiftodo-task-list-for-todo.txt/id1073798440?ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;in the App Store&lt;/a&gt;. It improves hardware keyboard support in the task list and task editor. Now you can type the first character to make picking priority, project, and context faster.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 09:36:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/133656.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/133656.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Once again, a macOS point update has stalled on my old MacBook Pro. It has been stuck for nearly 8 hours. I guess I will force reboot (later) and cross my fingers that it comes back to life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 08:22:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/once-again-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/once-again-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hot take: Swift 4.1 is .1 better than Swift 4.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:06:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/29/hot-take-swift.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/30/hot-take-swift.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s a big Apple software update day today! iOS 11.3 and Xcode 9.3 &lt;em&gt;finally&lt;/em&gt; were released. I hope the new Xcode works out more of the Swift-related kinks. Xcode 9.2 still can’t jump to many of my method definitions, and I’ve never understood why.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:18:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/29/its-a-big.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mjdescy.micro.blog/2018/03/29/its-a-big.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
